本字幕 由 首發字幕組 原創翻譯
本電影由 BT首發論壇 原創壓制
www.BTshoufa.com
更多超清電影下載盡在 BT首發論壇
我向妳們宣誓，
I swear to you,
在我們當中
every single mother and daughter,
被黑死病所殺害的每壹對母女，每壹對父子
father and son taken from us
都將可以復仇
by the Black Plague will be avenged.
這是他們的女巫王
It is their Witch Queen
給我們這片大陸帶來詛咒的人
who brought this curse upon our lands.
她死後我們就能得到解放了
And in her death lies our salvation.
小心點，兄弟
Be warned, brothers.
她不會真正的死去
She will never truly perish
除非她的心臟停止跳動
until her heart beats its last.
我們不要害怕
Let fear be dead to us.
我們沒有回頭路了
There is no going back,
也沒什麽好回頭的
for there is nothing to go back to.
這是什麽，多蘭？
What is it, Dolan?
我們周圍充滿了魔法
The Hexen are amongst us.
這個地方散發著死亡的氣息
This place reeks of death.
大家要更註意點
Keep your wits about you.
別走散了
Stay close.
是她！
It's her!
是女巫王！
It's the Queen!
這是魔法
The magic.
不要靠近
Stay back!
用冷兵器和火!
By iron and fire!
救我們！
Help us!
-多蘭！-女巫王！
- Dolan! - The Queen!
天父，
Heavenly Father,
保護我們免受惡魔的傷害。
protect us from these demons.
啊！
Ah!
保持陣型，兄弟！
Stay in formation, men!
爸爸！
Father!
爸爸，我好想妳
Father, I missed you.
妳不是真的
You're not real.
妳不可能是
You can't be.
妳們像老鼠壹樣繁殖
You breed like rats.
妳們把石頭疊起來
You put stone on top of stone
然後住在裏面
and then live in your own filth.
妳們是這個世界的入侵者
You are trespassers on our world.
這就是我制造瘟疫的原因
This is why I created the Plague.
這就是妳們必須滅亡的原因
It's why every one of you must perish.
啊！
Ah!
用冷兵器
By iron
和火
and fire.
妳愛的每個人都已經死了
Everyone you love is gone.
翻譯：Tony  YAfish  Jolion Chan  莫夏  萱lo2e  fyemee  校對 ：真中
我在妳眼裏看到了
I've seen it in your eyes.
妳希望死去
You wish for death.
今天我們倆都會死
Today we both die.
我用我的生命來詛咒妳
I curse you with life.
永遠看不到和平
To never know peace.
永遠的孤獨的活在這個世上
To walk the Earth alone for eternity.
妳永遠不會死
You will never die.
謝謝妳
Thank you.
打擾壹下，小姐？
Excuse me, miss?
先生，需要什麽幫助？
Sir, how can I help you?
魔法
Magic.
嘿...
Hey...
看這個！
Watch it!
對不起，都是我的錯
Sorry. Totally my fault.
打擾壹下
Excuse me.
妳是女巫獵人
You're the witch hunter.
是的
Yeah.
我什麽都沒做
I didn't do anything.
讓我們看看這個
Let's see it.
看什麽？
See what?
來吧
Come on.
女士們先生們，
Ladies and gentlemen,
飛機遇到突發情況...
the Captain has turned on...
很高興妳沒弄濕它們
Be glad you didn't get them wet.
我找這些東西找了壹段時間了
I've been looking for these for a while.
這是古時候留下來的
These are ancient runes.
它們能控制天氣
They can manipulate weather.
下雨，刮風，寒冷，高溫...
Rain, wind, cold, heat...
妳就這樣把它們包在壹起扔在包裏？
And you just jammed them together in your bag?
妳知道在4萬尺的高空
You know what you get when you mix a thunderstorm
雷暴和潮濕的寒冷空氣混在壹起會發生什麽事嗎？
with cool, moist air at 40,000 feet?
這是很簡單的科學常識
It's simple science.
難以置信
Unbelievable.
作為壹個女巫妳竟然不知道妳有什麽樣的能力
You witches have no idea the power you've got.
噢，我的天
Oh, my God.
妳會把我抓到女巫委員會嗎？
Are you gonna turn me over to the Witch Council?
不
No.
妳要殺了我？
You're gonna kill me?
殺了妳？
Kill you?
我阻止了妳殺了妳自己
I'm tryin' to stop you from killing yourself.
在紐約好好玩吧
Enjoy New York.
先生，“系好安全帶”的信號燈在亮著
Sir, "Fasten seatbelts" signs are on.
妳要坐回去
I need you to take a seat.
我叫考爾德
My name is Kaulder.
妳要坐回妳的位置，考爾德
I need you to get back to your seat, Kaulder.
我很高興聽到在塞夫魯長大的人的聲音
I'd love to hear about growing up in Sefrou.
妳怎麽知道？
How'd you know?
這幾年都沒有口音了
Haven't had an accent in years.
我在生命中遇到了很多人
I've met a lot of people in my life.
對此妳很驚訝吧
You'd be amazed what you pick up.
女巫在我們之中秘密的生活
Witches live among us in secret.
他們的魔法在從遠古的祖先中流傳下來
Their magic passed down from an ancient race,
衰弱了，大半遺忘了，但仍然危險而強大
diluted, half-forgotten, but dangerously powerful.
經過幾個世紀的沖突，簽署了停戰協議
After centuries of conflict, a truce was forged.
女巫允許正常生活並管理她們自己
Witches would be allowed to live
如果她們遵守壹個嚴格的規定
and govern themselves if they followed
就是魔法絕對不能對人類使用
one strict rule, that magic never be used against humans.
停火協議是很容易破壞的
But a truce is a fragile thing.
有些人渴望
There are some who long for
恢復以前那樣
the return of the old ways,
女巫王黑暗統治的日子
the dark days of the Witch Queen.
考爾德要處理的就是這些人
It is those whom Kaulder deals with.
八百多年來，他為十斧會幹活
For 800 years, he has served The Axe and Cross.
我們壹起看守和維護著和平
Together we have kept watch and kept the peace.
唉，對不起，多蘭神父。他在開會
Uh, I'm sorry, Father Dolan. He's in a meeting.
噢
Oh.
會議結束了
The meeting has concluded.
我以壹個特別的方式
I Serve The Axe and Cross
為十斧會服務
in a very different manner.
我是第36任多蘭，並撰寫了考爾德的歷史
I am the 36th Dolan, and I write Kaulder's history.
我是他的左右手，他的教徒
I am his handler, his confessor,
但是，我喜歡認為我是他的朋友
and, I like to think, his friend.
妳沒有時間意識
You have no sense of time.
我當然有，只是和妳的不太壹樣
Course I do. It's just different than yours.
我猜妳的任務完成了？
I assume your mission was a success?
妳安全的獲得了天氣符文
You recovered the weather runes without incident?
我給妳的ipad怎麽樣了？
What happened to the iPad I gave you?
我轉送給別人了
I re-gifted it.
我跟妳都不適合用這個
We're not all as adaptable as you.
妳知道紙張已經過時了
You know paper's the past.
記東西的時候仍然有用
It's also a useful object on which to record it.
妳還記得路德維希的事嗎？
Are you reminiscing about the Ludwig affair?
我現在心情不好
I'm in a sentimental mood.
啊
Ah.
關於我退休的事？
About my retirement?
這是妳回來的原因
That's why you've come back.
我們合作得很好
We have had a good run.
我們取締了壹些討厭的女巫會
We took out some nasty covens.
妳真的準備好退休了？
You're really ready to call it quits?
只工作了50年
It's only been 50 years.
我終於習慣了妳
I'm finally getting used to you.
噢，這就是妳要說的嗎？
Oh. Is that all it took?
我會想妳的，孩子
I'll miss you, kid.
這是華特曼402
This is a Waterman 402.
我把妳名字首字母刻上去了
I had your initials engraved on it.
它相當珍貴
It's very rare.
（把字母刻上去）可能會降低壹點價值
Probably lowered the value quite a bit.
對我來說不是
Not to me.
如果妳重新考慮，妳仍然能擁有這支筆
You reconsider, you can still keep the pen.
我認為妳會喜歡我的繼承人的。
I think you'll like my successor.
我留給妳壹個更現代的幫手
I'm leaving you in more modern hands.
妳的誓言怎麽樣？
What about the vow you took?
我發誓至死都會站在妳身邊
I vowed to face death at your side.
除非死去，不然我都會壹直工作
Not to work until I keel over.
在妳之前有35任多蘭
Thirty-five Dolans have come before you.
只有妳的建議
Here's to the only one
我才會聽聽
whose advice I ever listened to.
只是之後不采用
Only to ignore it.
但是我都有在聽
But I always listen.
要是妳也退休了呢？
What if you were retiring, too?
我是說，妳會做什麽
I mean, what would you do
如果下壹個任務是妳最後壹個？
if your next mission was your last?
但是不會
But it won't be.
回答壹下我的問題吧
Humor me.
我沒抱怨
I have no complaints.
每天我醒來
Every day I wake up,
這個世界更寧靜了些
the world sleeps a little easier.
考爾德，妳的人生經歷之豐
Kaulder, you have tasted more of life
比我能想象到的還要多
than I can ever imagine,
但是很長壹段時間了妳都沒真正的活著
but it's been a long time since you really lived.
在我們短暫的存活的這段時間裏
You're missing out on the best part
妳錯過了最好的壹段
of our brief stay in this world.
就是妳會跟人分享的這段時間
The part where you share it.
找壹個值得信任的人
Find someone to trust.
我相信妳
I trust you.
或許有人更合適
Perhaps someone a little more comely.
我知道，我沒有活的
I know, I haven't lived
像妳這麽長而豐富
as long and rich a life as you,
但是我知道
but I do know that there is more to it
空姐除了要到處旅行之外
than a parade of stewardesses
還會演奏悅耳的月光奏鳴曲
marching to the dulcet tones of Moonlight Sonata.
現在妳對於空姐
Now what in the world do you know
還知道些什麽？
about stewardesses anyway?
我不是牧師出生
I wasn't born a priest.
我們幹壹些活先吧
Let's do some work.
我知道妳認為這無聊
I know you think it's dull,
但是我們還是從頭開始吧
but let's start at the beginning.
壹句話都沒說就走了
It goes without saying,
但妳的工作真的超級棒
but you've served with great distinction.
如果可以的話，明天我見考爾夫的時候
If I may, when I meet Kaulder tomorrow,
我應該要做得很好才行，對吧？
I should play it cool, right?
在儀式結束前不喝咖啡
No coffee until after the ritual.
不要為妳的風格擔心
Don't worry about your style.
他怎樣都會給妳難堪的
He'll take the piss out of you anyway.
但是妳會沒事的
But you'll be fine.
這就是，唉，我擔心考爾德的地方。
It's, uh, Kaulder that I worry about.
妳擔心考爾德？
You worry about Kaulder?
妳知道十斧會的長者
Do you know how the elders
怎樣評價他嗎？
of The Axe and Cross refer to him?
他們說他是“武器”
They call him "The Weapon."
在我提交報告的時候
When I put in my reports,
他們都只想知道數字而已
all they want to know is numbers.
我拘留了多少個女巫
How many witches I've turned over for detention.
殺死了多少個違法的
How many slain for breaking the law.
這妳能怪他們嗎？他所做的都是很重要的
Can you blame them? What he does is so important.
是的，這是事實，但是他不僅僅是個武器
Yes, that's true, but he isn't just a weapon.
而我們是那些知道真相的人
And those of us who know the truth,
我們承擔著責任
we bear responsibility.
不管發生什麽事情，向我保證妳要看護好他
Whatever happens, promise me you'll watch out for him.
當然，那是我的工作
Of course. That's my job.
出租車！
Taxi!
餵？
Hello?
考爾德？
Kaulder?
多蘭36世在昨晚安詳地去世了
Dolan the 36th passed away peacefully last night.
明天會舉行葬禮
The ceremony will be tomorrow.
請節哀順變
I'm sorry for your loss.
在妳前面已經有36任多蘭
Thirty-six have taken the name "Dolan" before you.
妳是否能配的上第37任這個稱號
Are you worthy of becoming the 37th?
我會證明給妳看我配得上
I testify that I am.
妳願意承諾
Do you promise to serve
不顧壹切的為我們的考爾德履行職責麽？
our brother Kaulder in all things?
會像他了解他自己那樣去了解他嗎？
To know him only as he knows himself?
我願意
I promise.
所以，妳是新人咯
So you're the new guy.
我們之前其實見過
We've actually met before.
很久很久以前
A long time ago.
妳看到那塊基石嗎？
You see that cornerstone?
我見人們把它立在那裏的時候
I watched them lay it in
那裏無非是塊玉米地
when this was nothing more than a cornfield.
那才是很久很久以前
That was a long time ago.
我作為第37任多蘭使者，願意誓死效忠妳
I pledge my life and loyalty to you as the 37th Dolan.
我發誓我會幫妳履行妳的使命...
I swear to help you carry out your duty to the Order...
當初在建造這個城市的時候
When they were building this city,
建築工人在地下60英尺發現了
construction crews discovered
壹個大墓地
a mass gravesite, 60 feet below ground,
裏面都是那些被遺忘的奴隸
filled with thousands of forgotten slaves.
知道他們之後怎麽做嗎？
Know what they did?
不知道
No.
他們連夜把這些坑都埋了
Worked by night, filled the hole,
然後繼續蓋樓
and kept building.
到處都是惡魔的身影
There are shades of evil everywhere.
所以，我幫妳辦了
So, I'm sorting you out with
新的信用卡，新的護照和新的身份證
fresh credit cards, new passport, and a new identity.
習慣了用舊的了
Just gettin' used to the old one.
喔，那都過期了
Well, it's out of date.
現在全球資料庫已經是壹體化了，閉路電視
There are global databases now, CCTV's,
手機，位置追蹤。世界壹直在改變
smartphones and geotracking. The world is changing.
只僅僅在表面而已
Only on the surface.
沒錯，但是保持低調是很重要的。
Right. But it's important to keep a low profile.
嗯嗯
Mmm-hmm.
唉。。
Uh...
我想我們應該感激它不是紅色的
I guess we should be thankful it's not red.
現在我們去哪？
May I ask where we're going?
我看過人們變老，退休，然後逝去
I've seen people get old, retire, and die.
但都發生在同壹天卻很少
Rarely on the same day.
他在桌子上被發現的
He was found at his desk.
我們在找什麽？
What are we looking for?
妳怎麽知道附近什麽時候有人施展魔法？
How do you know when there's magic in the vicinity?
施展女巫的魔法來自四種元素
A witch's magic comes from four elements,
火，水，土和空氣
fire, water, earth and air.
運用正確的煉金術觸發器
Applying the correct alchemical triggers
會暴露曾經施法的痕跡
will reveal its presence.
這裏沒有使用魔法
No magic here.
只是想確認壹下
Just wanted to be sure.
如果窗口是關的
If the window hasn't been opened,
這些蟲子是怎麽進來的？
how did that get in here?
壹只的話可以忽略
One means nothing.
兩只的話可以說是巧合
Two, a coincidence.
三只就意味著麻煩事了
Three, trouble.
趴下！
Get down!
什麽？
What?
他是被巫師殺死的
He was killed by witches.
在歷史上十斧會的多蘭
Never in the history of The Axe and Cross
從來沒有被謀殺過
has a Dolan ever been murdered.
妳想退出嗎？
You wanna quit?
不想
No.
我想加人工
I want a raise.
這是在宣戰
This is a declaration of war.
誰會做這些事？
Who could have done this?
施展這隱秘的魔法是為了
A concealment spell was placed
讓所有東西都看起來很自然
to make everything look normal.
他們在找
They were searching for something,
壹些不想讓我們知道的東西
didn't want us to know.
元素魔法是中立的
Elemental magic is neutral.
從根本上既不是善的也不是惡的。
At its root it's neither good nor evil.
但是這不同
But this is different.
這些是黑魔法
This is dark magic.
淩駕於魔鬼
Beyond evil.
他們把他綁在椅子上
They tied him to the chair.
“死”
"Death."
這是咒語的壹部分嗎？
Is that part of the spell?
妳在他死之前到過這裏，對嗎？
You were here last night before he died, right?
是啊
Yes.
讓我看看妳的手
Let me see your hands.
馬上
Now.
我5歲的時候
I was five years old
女巫們把我們的屋子燒了
when witches set our house on fire.
我的父母被燒死
My parents died.
但是妳走進大火裏
But you walked through the flames,
用毯子把我卷起來
wrapped me in a blanket,
然後從二樓的窗口跳出去
and jumped out the second story window.
用身體墊著我著地
Your body broke the fall.
我已經告訴過妳我們之前見過
I told you we'd met before.
如果妳不記得，我從頭細說
If you don't remember, I can refer you to the entry...
不用了，我記得
No. I remember.
妳追捕那些女巫和給他們應有的懲罰
You hunted down the witches and brought them to justice.
我等了壹輩子就是為了得到這個機會去幫助妳
I've waited my entire life for the opportunity to help you.
那好，現在機會來了
Well, now's your chance.
妳可以幫助我追捕幹這事的女巫了
You can help me hunt the witches that did this.
我不應該要有壹把槍或者鐵棒之類的東西嗎？
Shouldn't I have a gun or an iron mallet or something?
深呼吸下，集中精神。
Take a deep breath. Center yourself.
好，當然如此
Right. Of course.
因為抵抗魔法需要清醒的頭腦
Because resisting enchantment requires a clear mind.
馬克斯是14級的巫師
Now, Max is a 14th level warlock,
沒有什麽東西是妳可以做的。可以放松壹下。
there's nothing you can do. May as well relax.
免費試吃，神父？
Free sample, Father?
噢，謝謝
Oh. Thank you.
吃之前我都要再三考慮壹下
I'd think twice about that.
只有1萬塊我不知道能不能做哦
I don't know that I can do $10,000.
妳知道這個級別的魔法
You know the level of enchantment
其他人都這個價
they are getting from that.
我們的交易沒問題，對吧？
Business is good, right?
好吧
Yeah.
噢，槽糕
Oh, crap.
到點關門了，馬克斯
Shop's closed, Max.
考爾德，好久不見了
Kaulder. It has been too long.
售賣變思蟲不是違法的
It is not illegal to sell mind-altering bugs.
當他們用在人類身上，這就是非法的
When they're used on humans, it is.
他們融入到蛋糕裏面
They're mixing them in the cupcakes.
我沒有留意
I hadn't noticed.
知道這個嗎？
Notice this?
格裏芬的天仙子，非常稀罕而且是禁止采摘的
Griffin's Henbane. Very rare and forbidden.
他們被用在通靈術上，黑魔法
This is used in necromancy. Dark magic.
妳知道我從來都不做這類壞事
You know I do not deal in these kinds of bad things.
馬克斯，妳足夠聰明不會走上這條路
Max, you're too smart to go down that road.
誰能想象我被騙了多少次
One can only imagine how many times I've been lied to.
超過歷史上的任何人，實際上
More than anyone in history, actually.
得了吧，考爾德
Come on, Kaulder.
妳必須明白，誰用上這種草藥
You must understand, anyone who would use this herb
都是不怕妳的。那才是讓我害怕的！
is not afraid of you. And that scares me!
比我還讓妳害怕？
More than I scare you?
馬克斯
Max.
來見我的那個人皮膚有壹種氣味
The man who came to see me has an odor on his skin.
壹種像大蒜但是不是大蒜的氣味
A whiff of garlic that was not garlic.
砒霜。還有麽？
Arsenic. Anything else?
還有腐朽怨蘋果。
And moldering crabapples.
多謝妳，馬克斯
Thank you, Max.
小心點
Be careful.
沒有那習慣
Not in the habit.
不是妳。是他。
Not you. Him.
所以這些對妳有什麽啟發嗎？
So, all that made sense to you?
這對妳沒有什麽啟發麽？
It didn't to you?
沒有
No.
砒霜在內戰裏是用來防腐的
Arsenic was used for embalming back in the Civil War.
殺了多蘭的人曾經
Whoever killed Dolan
住在以前是葬禮堂的地方
is likely living in what was once a funeral parlor.
我們只需要找到有腐朽蘋果樹的地方就可以了
We just have to find one with a crabapple tree.
這是幹嘛的？
What's that for?
乘車用的
A cab.
妳不勝任接下來發生的事情
You're not qualified for what happens next.
噢
Oh.
好的。我會開收據的
Right. I'll get a receipt.
哇嗷
Whoa.
妳媽媽沒有教妳
Didn't your mother ever teach you
不要吃樹上的糖果麽？
not to eat candy from trees?
回家吧，孩子
Go home, kid.
走開
Go away.
沒事的
It's okay.
走開
- Get away from me. - Shh.
沒事的
It's okay.
快給我走開
Get away from me now.
我不會傷害妳的。走開！
- I'm not gonna hurt you. - Go away!
沒事的
It's okay.
啊...
Ah...
噢，我靠
Oh, shit.
是妳殺了多蘭。為什麽？
You killed Dolan. Why?
誰是那該死的多蘭？啊？
Who the bloody hell's Dolan? Huh?
我這輩子從來沒見過他！
I never met the man in my life!
妳喜歡我的新筆嗎？啊？
Do you like my new pen? Huh?
當我想像在委員會面前
When I imagined my first prosecution
第壹次起訴
in front of the Council,
我是從來沒想過
I never thought it would be
是壹起針對我們的案件
for a crime against one of our own.
艾裏克·雷曼斯奈
Ellic Lemasniel.
妳好，神父。喔！
Hello, Father. Whoo!
妳看起來很好人
You look like a good man,
很好吃的樣子，妳，我從來沒。。。
tasty little thing, you. I never went...
請不要小看我
Please don't think less of me.
我遲點會認錯的了
I'll confess it later.
巫師委員會會接收妳的了
The Witch Council receives you,
十斧會第37任多蘭使者。
37th Dolan of The Axe and Cross.
和平永存
The peace endures.
我現在把殺害第36任多蘭使者的被告
I present the accused,
艾裏克·雷曼斯奈
Ellic Lemasniel, for judgment,
帶給妳們審判
for the murder of Dolan the 36th.
我現在呈上在被告住所找到的證物
I present the evidence found in the accused's dwelling.
找到的？噢，拜托
Found? Oh, come on.
什麽？妳們看起來就像80年代那群糟糕的樂隊
What? You look like a terrible band from the '80s.
看看妳那頭發！
Look at your hair!
他會得到應有的罪名的
He will be judged.
等等等等......
Blah, blah, blah.
妳知道我的曾祖父的曾祖父
You know my great-grandfather's
曾經伺候過女王嗎，啊？
grandfather served The Queen, huh?
女王
The Queen.
妳們都是官僚主義的酒囊飯袋
You're a bureaucracy o' cowards
我不會承認
and I don't recognize the authority
在這個委員會上的權威
here in this council.
我也不會遵守妳們的法律
Nor do I abide by your law.
法律服務來控制和維持魔法的
The laws serve to control and contain magic.
只有通過這個委員會的運作
It is only by the operations of this council
另壹個戰爭才不會發生
that another war does not begin.
我沒撒謊！我為我所做的感到自豪
I won't lie! I'm proud of what I done!
我殺害了妳們的牧師
I murdered your priest!
我滴水滴幹他，他就像壹只蠢豬
I drip-dried him like he was a stuck pig!
我們的牧師，和我的朋友
Our priest, and my friend.
考爾德
Kaulder.
哦，糟糕，又是這家夥
Oh, shit. This guy again.
所以我們沒有審訊也要審判他？
So we're to judge him without interrogation?
有人問過他，他給誰工作嗎？
Has anyone asked him who he was workin' with?
沒有三個五芒星卡
There's no Three of Pentacles card.
那就意味著他獨自工作
That means he worked alone.
這些卡都是錯的
The cards are wrong.
他施了壹個形狀轉換的咒語
He cast a shape-shifting spell.
800年來我都我沒見過那玩意兒
I haven't seen that crafted in 800 years.
自從女巫王的時代之後
Not since the time of the Witch Queen.
哈！女巫王死了很久了
Ha! The Witch Queen is long dead.
她的魔法是不可能重現的
That her magic could return is impossible.
- 不可能嗎? - 是的
- Is it impossible? - It is.
- 妳擁有權威... - 已經足夠了
- You have the authority... - Enough!
把這個城市顛倒
To Turn this city inside out.
對於非法制造罪
For the crimes of illegal crafting...
找出他是和誰壹起工作
Find who he's working with.
和人間的祭祀
And human sacrifice...
- 我為我所做的感到自豪 - 我們宣判
- And I'm proud o' what I done. - We sentence...
艾裏克·雷曼斯奈
Ellic Lemasniel...
我為我所做的感到驕傲
I'm proud o' what I done.
- 監禁 - 我立場堅定
- To incarceration... - I took a stand!
在這房間基石的下方
In the bedrock beneath this chamber.
妳是悲哀的...的反映
You are sad reflections of...
蘇醒吧，哨兵
Arise, Sentinel,
把犯人帶進監獄
and carry the condemned to prison.
妳將永遠不見天日
You'll never see daylight again.
不不！妳現在可能會抓了我
No, no! You may hold me now,
但是妳們將永遠不會把我們全部抓住
but you'll never have us all!
那是什麽
What is that?
嘿  孩子
Hey, kid.
妳在幹什麽
What are you doing?
妳好，神父
Hello, Father.
仍然跟我們在壹起，老朋友
Still with us, old friend.
他還活著嗎
He's alive?
僅僅活著
Barely.
他被詛咒了
He's been cursed.
怎麽的？
How?
蒼蠅座 馬裏
Musca Mali.
瘟疫橫飛
Plague fly.
十三世紀的黑魔法
13th-century black magic.
它們是在女巫王的時候的樹上被創造出的，對嗎？
They were created in the tree of the Queen, correct?
是的
That's right.
為什麽他們沒有殺了他？
Why didn't they just murder him?
他們想審判他
They wanted to interrogate him.
當瘟疫駐紮在妳身體裏
When a Plague fly burrows inside of you,
就會破壞妳的意識
it breaks your will.
無論兇手想知道什麽
Whatever the killers wanted to know,
他都會告訴他們
he would have told them.
但問題依然存在，他們想知道什麽？
But the question remains, what did they want to know?
他沒有蘇醒起來
He isn't getting up.
除非我們能打破詛咒
Not unless we could break the curse.
打破詛咒的唯壹方法
And the only way to do that
就是殺了施法的女巫
is to kill the witch who cast it.
讓艾裏克為他賣命的那個
The one Ellic works for.
他頂多還有兩天
Dolan's got two days, tops.
為了我，堅持住
Hang in there, for me.
死亡
"Death."
這是多蘭留下的信息,而不是殺手的
It's a message from Dolan, not the killer.
回想起妳的死亡
"Remember your death."
什麽意思
What does it mean?
只有壹個方式回想起我的死亡
There's only one way to remember my death...
魔法
Magic.
嘿，克洛伊
Hey, Chloe.
我這裏還有壹杯酒
I have one more drink here.
- 大家還好嗎 -是的 ,我們都很好
- Are you guys okay? - Yeah, we're good.
我們會有壹個很美好的晚上對吧，先生們？
Are we having a good night, gentlemen?
我們來談談戀愛吧，寶貝
Do a love shot with me, baby.
噢，不，我今晚不想談戀愛
Oh, no. I'm not looking for love tonight.
- 大家都還好嗎 -是的
- You guys okay? - Yep.
- 還想再要壹個嗎 - 好的
- Want another one? - All right.
哦，不，拜托！不，也不是妳
Oh, no, come on! No, not you, too.
我聽說妳也不知道會發生什麽事。好嗎？
I heard that you can't tell before it happens. Okay?
他只是冰冷的站在那，然後...
He's just standing there all chilly calm, and then...
砰！他砍下妳的頭
Wham! He cuts your head off
把它掛在他的腰帶上
and puts it in a sack on his belt.
拜托！這只是壹個保姆告訴孩子們的故事
C'mon! That's just a story nannies tell children
讓他們聽話而已
so they behave.
克洛伊,妳得離開了
Chloe, you need to leave.
米蘭達  米蘭達
Miranda. Miranda!
我們遵守法律，這裏沒有人類
We're up to code. There are no humans here.
好地方
Beautiful place.
謝謝妳
Thank you.
妳要多少錢
How much do you charge?
唉，那得看妳買什麽了
Well, that depends on what you're buying.
壹個回憶
A memory.
500美金
Five hundred dollars.
成交
Deal.
我剛剛說的是“百”嗎 ？我...
Did I just say "Hundred"? I...
不, 妳知道嗎? 我真實的意思是“五千”。
No, you know what? I actually meant "Five thousand."
5000元,這就是妳的意思對吧？
Five thousand, is that what you meant?
對，就是五千
I did. I meant "Five thousand."
成交
Sold.
5萬塊
Fifty thousand.
我們可以開始了麽？
Shall we start?
不行，妳知道麽？不行。
No. You know what? No.
我改主意了。我們...
I changed my mind. We're cl...
恐懼藥劑
Fear potion.
在這個世界上還有什麽是妳害怕的？
Now, what in the world would you be afraid of?
公眾演講
Public speaking.
妳知道我害怕什麽？
You know what I'm afraid of?
說吧
Enlighten me.
我什麽都不怕。這很無聊，真的。
Nothing. It's boring, really.
妳看，我知道妳們有法律
See now, I know that you have a code.
我還知道我並沒有做錯什麽
And I also know that I haven't done anything wrong,
所以除非妳拿把槍指在我的頭上，不然就滾出去
so unless you're gonna put a gun to my head, get out.
妳說的沒錯。我是有法律
You know, you're right. I do have a code.
但我並不會離開
But I'm also not leaving.
不管怎麽說，妳究竟要回憶劑幹什麽？
What do you want a memory potion for, anyway?
妳是正在狩獵女巫嗎？
Are you hunting a witch?
去救壹個老朋友
To help an old friend.
給妳壹句忠告
But a word of warning to you.
如果妳在妳的記憶中受傷
If you get injured in your memory,
妳也會在現實中受到同樣的傷害
you get injured out here.
這意味著如果妳在記憶中死去的話
Which means to say that if you die in there,
妳真的會死...
you will also die...
我在哪都不會死
I can't die anywhere.
為了我的安全我必須跟妳說清楚
I have to make a disclaimer for my insurance.
開啟按鈕啦
Bottoms up.
說“女巫獵人”
Say "Witch hunter."
女巫獵人
Witch hunter.
要乖乖的哦
Be nice.
回憶起妳的死
"Remember your death."
妳究竟想讓我看到什麽
What did you want me to see?
考爾德！
Kaulder!
考爾德。
Kaulder.
考爾德，醒醒。
Kaulder, wake up.
妳好，女巫獵人
Well, hello, witch hunter.
我曾經有壹次在回憶魔法中被叫醒
I was yanked out of a memory spell once.
幾個小時之內我分不清東南西北
My mind was scrambled eggs for hours.
要知道，人們就不應該亂翻他們的記憶
You know, people shouldn't root around in their past.
壹些東西最好被遺忘掉
Some things are best left forgotten.
唉...
Ah...
妳詛咒了我的朋友
You cursed my friend.
妳的朋友
Your friend,
他比大多數人只多堅持5分鐘
he lasted about five minutes longer than most.
在酒吧打架的時候別拿太多的武器
Doesn't take much balls to get in a bar fight
妳不會受傷
when you can't get hurt.
不幸的是，妳的意誌
Too bad your mind isn't as tough
並沒有妳其他部分強壯
as the rest of you.
不要再去酒吧了
No more bar.
別再使用記憶藥劑了
No more memory potions for you.
把它吸進去
Breathe.
800年之後，妳將要死了
After 800 years, you've run out of time.
死亡已經來臨，巫師獵人！
Death is coming, witch hunter!
妳就是他們說的怪物
You are the monster they say you are.
見鬼！這是我的全部！
Damn you! This place was all I had!
克洛伊
Chloe!
抓住我的手！
Grab my hand!
好美的景色
Nice view.
堅持住，孩子
Just hold on, kid.
我保證我會找到誰對妳做了這些還會打破詛咒。
I promise I'll find who did this and break the curse.
考爾德！過來看壹下！
Kaulder! Come see this!
我已經黑入了FBI網上數據庫
I've got the FBI database online.
停下，上壹條
Stop, go back one.
繼續
Continuing.
不，不是他
No, not him.
停
Stop.
是他
That's him.
但是為什麽他不想我去回憶我的死亡呢？
But why doesn't he want me to remember my death?
伯恩·巴爾塔薩·凱托拉
Born Baltasar Ketola.
現用名是彼列，芬蘭國籍。
Goes by Belial. Finnish national.
艾裏克就是為他工作的
He's the one Ellic was working for.
他就是那個詛咒多蘭的人？
The one who cursed Dolan?
每壹代人都會被賜予
Every generation has to be given
毀滅世界的機會
their chance to destroy the world.
但是大部分人不會像他壹樣，妳知道
Yet most of us aren't like him, you know.
我們和妳壹樣
We're the same as you.
妳可能看起來像我們，但是妳並不是
You may look like us, but you're not.
妳的血液蘊含著魔法的力量
You've got magic in your blood.
能做非常壞的事的魔法
Magic that can do very bad things.
我們在妳的酒吧被打斷了
We were interrupted back in your bar.
- 對沒錯。 - 我必須要在嘗試壹次。
- Oh, yes. - I have to try again.
對了，我的酒吧！
Yes, my bar!
我所在乎的所有東西都被燒成了灰燼
Where everything I cared about burnt to the ground.
但是我並沒有責怪妳毀滅了
But I'm not blaming you for destroying
我的生活或什麽東西
my life or anything.
我僅僅是在看著
I'm just making an observation.
看著妳毀掉我的生活
An observation on how you destroyed my life.
我要走了
I'm leaving.
聽著，我就像妳壹樣不喜歡那樣
Look, I don't like it any more than you do,
但是如果妳能幫助我，我保證我會保證妳安全
but if you help me, I promise to keep you safe.
我需要更多的斯諾登尼亞水
I'll need more Snowdonia hawkweed
來制作另壹個記憶藥劑
to mix another memory potion.
米蘭達，那個為我工作的女孩
Miranda, the girl who works for me,
有壹個非常好的儲藏室
has a pretty good stash.
唉，我發個信息給他
Um, I'll text her.
謝謝
Thank you.
彼列的夾克上有紅色的土壤
Belial had red soil on his jacket.
紅土？
Red soil?
分析壹下看我們能從中得到什麽線索。
Analyze this and see what we get.
當然
Of course.
米蘭達打過來的。
It's Miranda.
她是愛貓人
She's a cat person.
海！海，妳好
Hey! Hey, there.
不，我還沒死。
No, I'm not dead yet.
好了，當她到這裏的時候
Right, so when she gets here,
不要做任何突然的動作，可以麽？
don't make any sudden moves, okay?
不要有眼神接觸
Don't make eye contact.
或者和她說話
Or talk.
哇
Whoa.
不好意思
Sorry.
這個就是了
This is it here.
不是，它還沒有發芽
No, it hasn't sprouted yet.
妳壹共加入了多少個
How many witch hunter
巫師獵人討論小組？
discussion groups are you a part of?
嗜殺、不朽的法西斯
"Genocidal immortal fascist..."
這就是妳們女巫師眼中的我，是麽？
So that's what you witches think of me, huh?
不管怎麽說人們眼中的我們又是什麽？
What is it that people know about us, anyway?
綠色的皮膚
That we have green skin
喜歡戴尖帽子，
and like to wear pointy hats,
然後我們是卑鄙的
and that we're mean
應該被綁在教堂的柱子上燒死？
and got burned at the stake in Salem?
教會錯了
Salem was wrong,
那些女人是無辜的
and those women innocent.
但是如果那些女人真的是巫師呢？
But what if those women really were witches?
那是不是這樣對待她們就是正確的呢？
Would it then have been okay?
我有時就在想如果我被發現有罪
See, I remember thinking if it was me found guilty,
沒人會關心的
no one would care.
我會
I would.
水蘭不見了。它不見了。
The hawkweed's gone. It's gone.
我意思是說有人把它拿走了。它不在這。
I mean, someone's taken it. It's not here.
考爾德？
Kaulder?
怎麽了？
What?
- 什麽？- 不
- What? - No.
米蘭達。
Miranda.
米蘭達！
Miranda!
妳來遲了，巫師獵人。
You're too late, witch hunter.
她死的很痛苦，不停的尖叫
She died badly, screaming.
孤獨
Alone.
妳也會跟她壹樣
Just like you will.
妳壹定會抓到這個人的，是不是？
You're gonna get who did this, right?
我要搞定彼列
I'll handle Belial.
很好
Good.
我不知道還有什麽地方可以找到我們需要的東西
I don't know where else to get the stuff that we need.
還有壹個地方
There is one place.
但是那裏用舊幣，古老的魔法並且危險。
But it's old money, old magic, and dangerous.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
考爾德？
Kaulder?
桑婭
Sonya.
丹妮現在真的很忙
Danique's been so busy,
我很驚訝她會妳
I'm surprised that she agreed to see you.
我不認為她會喜歡
I don't think she would have liked
另壹個選擇
the alternative.
考爾德先生，妳預定了我的夜晚
Mr. Kaulder, you've made my night.
請坐
Please have a seat.
妳從哪裏救得小朋友，壹個舊貨商店？
Where'd you rescue your little friend from, a thrift shop?
- 小朋友....- 噢...
- Little friend... - Oh...
告訴我吧，什麽緊急情況？
So tell me, what is this emergency?
什麽是妳必須要回憶起來的？
What is it you just must remember?
他丟了他的車鑰匙
He lost his car keys.
妳要多少錢?
How much do I owe you?
壹分錢不收。妳只需跟我喝壹杯就行了
Oh, nothing. You have a drink with me. That's my price.
妳知道我來這裏是幹什麽的
You know what I'm here for.
太多人把自己偽裝成壹個不真實的自己
So many of us pretend to be something that we're not.
但是妳，妳活了這麽久
But you, you've lived.
穿越了整個歷史
A man who's walked through history.
見過拿破侖，斯大林，
To have known Napoleon, Stalin,
希特勒
Hitler...
不需要懷舊他們。已經有夠多的壞蛋了
No need to be nostalgic. We have enough evil now.
他們跟妳很不壹樣
They're not so different than you.
他們用他們的力量來改變這個世界
They used their power to change the world.
而妳做了之後並不能改變什麽
You can't change what you've done.
考爾德！這棵植物有點古怪
Kaulder! There's something wrong with this plant.
妳在這裏
You're here.
考爾德...
Kaulder...
考爾德！考爾德！
Kaulder! Kaulder!
- 享受天堂吧。-考爾德！
- Enjoy paradise. - Kaulder!
考爾德，那是煙。不要
Kaulder, it's smoke. Don't...
看，爸爸。快看！
Look, Daddy. Look!
它們飛往南方過冬
They're flying south for the winter.
考爾德，聽我說
Kaulder, listen to me.
妳掉入陷阱了我需要妳現在醒過來
You are in a trap and I need you to wake up.
妳在這裏肯定找不到任何答案
You're not gonna find any answers here.
妳呆的時間越長越難以逃脫
The longer you wait, the harder it is to get out.
考爾德，考爾德
Kaulder. Kaulder.
我要妳現在就醒過來，這些都不是真的
I need you to wake up. None of this is real.
考爾德，妳掉進陷阱裏面了！
Kaulder, you are in a trap!
快回來
Come back.
考爾德，如果妳不能馬上醒來
Kaulder, if you don't wake up right now,
我們都會死在這裏！
we are both going to die!
給我醒醒！
Wake up!
克洛伊....
Chloe...
這不是真的
This isn't real.
考爾德！快醒過來！
Kaulder! Wake up!
把車停到小巷子裏
Pull the car into the alley
把他丟到後備箱
and throw him in the trunk.
我們會將會被載入史冊
We're going down in history
作為打倒巫師獵人的人
as the ones who beat the witch hunter.
搞定他
Come on.
出去
Get out.
墓地的泥土
Burial dirt.
用這個來施展黑魔法是厲害的了
Nothing more powerful for dark magic.
彼列要用這個幹啥？
What does Belial want with it?
誰？
Who?
“回憶起我的死亡”
"Remember my death."
他不想讓我看的是什麽
What is it that he doesn't want me to see?
停下！求妳了
Stop! Please.
彼列什麽都沒和我說
Belial didn't tell me anything.
我幫他弄到了泥土
I helped him get the dirt.
我只是給自己留了壹點點
I just took a little bit for myself.
他有特別多
He has tons of it.
請饒了我？
Please?
謝謝妳的酒
Thanks for the drink.
妳是種族的叛徒
You are a traitor to your kind!
妳知道我最喜歡舊貨店裏的什麽嗎？
You know what I like about thrift shops?
舊貨店裏什麽都是舊的
Everything in them is old.
哦!
Oh!
婊子！
Bitch.
所以先在妳知道了
So now you know.
妳是壹個夢行者。
You're a dream-walker.
每個人都知道夢行是黑色天賦
Everyone knows that dream-walking is a black gift.
我壹輩子都在躲著這個天賦
I've spent my entire life trying to hide from it.
妳知道我會發現妳的秘密，但是妳不在乎
You knew I would discover your secret, and you didn't care.
妳還是把我從陷阱中拉出來
You still pulled me out of that trap.
膽兒夠大的
It was a very brave thing to do.
給妳看點東西，過來。
Let me show you something. Come on.
晚安，馬克思！
Good night, Max!
妳是我們種族的恥辱
You are a disgrace to our kind.
彼列，我毫無選擇
Belial, I had no choice.
考爾德威脅要徒手揍死我
Kaulder threatened to beat me to death with his bare hands.
叛徒，我們幫妳弄了個計劃
We have plans for you, traitor.
彼列，妳要諒解我
You must understand, Belial.
在陰暗裏永劫不覆吧
Enjoy the shadows.
這就是巫師的歷史。妳們的歷史
This is the history of witches. Your history.
這是妳
That's you.
嗯
Yeah.
至少，他們沒把妳眼睛搞錯。
Least they got your eyes right.
這些是夢行者
These are the dream-walkers.
巫師皇後的致命殺手
The Witch Queen's deadliest assassins.
他們習慣於跳進妳的思維中
Somehow they used to jump into your mind
找出妳最珍貴的記憶
and pry out your most precious memories.
然後再把它們扭曲成噩夢
And then they'd twist 'em into your worst nightmares.
妳這是給我上歷史課呢?
What, you're giving a history lesson here
還是在嚇我？
or you're just trying to scare me?
夢行者的壹些事情別人並不知曉
There's something no one knows about dream-walkers.
他們並不需要記憶藥水
They don't need memory potions.
他們的力量是與生俱來的
That power lies within them.
我有些記憶被我深深掩埋了
I have something buried deep in my mind
但那些是我必須要回憶起的
that I must remember.
妳是唯壹可以幫助我的人
And you're the only one that can help me.
不，我不行
No, I can't.
克洛伊..
Chloe...
不，我不行
No, I can't.
妳知道，我還有個小弟弟
You know, I have a younger brother,
並且
and, uh,
他總能把我惹毛
he had this knack for just pissing me off.
有壹天他做得太過了
And one day he pushed it too far,
於是我就進入他的腦子裏
and I somehow entered his mind.
我傷害了他，我不是故意的
I hurt him. I didn't mean to,
但我傷害他很深
but I hurt him badly.
所以我逃跑了
So I ran away.
妳老婆和女兒的名字是什麽？
What were their names, your wife and daughter?
海倫娜
Helena.
伊麗莎白
Elizabeth.
我很久沒把他們的名字說出來了
I haven't said their names out loud in a long time.
考爾德，即使我想幫妳
Kaulder, even if I wanted to help you,
我也不知道怎麽開始
I wouldn't know where to begin.
想壹個和我倆都相關的詞
Think of a word that you associate with me.
可以是任何事
Could be anything.
清空妳的大腦
Empty everything else out of your head.
把註意力集中在那個詞
And just focus on that one word.
壹個詞
One word.
妳告訴我這個詞，我也把註意力集中在這個詞
If you tell me the word, I'll focus on it, too.
有時有用
Sometimes that helps.
哪個詞？
What's the word?
孤獨
Alone.
握著我的手
Take my hand.
這邊！
This way, men!
多蘭大哥，看
Brother Dolan, look.
考爾德
Kaulder.
那是什麽？多蘭？
What is that? Dolan?
小心走過去
Tread with care.
他做到了
He did it.
他了結了女巫王
So ends the Queen.
以神父之名...
In the name of the Father...
他被控制了！
He's possessed!
考爾德還活著
Kaulder is alive.
我們的噩夢奇跡般地結束了
Our nightmare ends with a miracle.
救救他
Help him.
是她的心
It's her heart.
我們摧毀了它，也就摧毀了她
When we destroy it, we destroy her.
多蘭大哥，了結了它
End it, Brother Dolan.
多蘭，殺了她！
Destroy her, Dolan!
不！
No!
妳把它留下了
You kept it.
結束了，女巫王死了
It's over. The Witch Queen is dead.
從壹開始他們就背叛了妳
They betrayed you from the start.
那就是他們要折磨妳朋友的原因
That's why they tortured your friend.
因為他知道那顆心臟在哪裏
Because he knew where the heart was.
他們想要將女巫王復活
They're gonna bring back the Queen.
過去800年間
For eight hundred years,
我們都在等待她的歸來
we've waited for her return.
妳應該感到榮耀，叛徒
You should be honored, traitor.
妳將會為了我們的事業而被獻祭
You will be sacrificed for our cause.
考爾德，我知道彼列在哪買的那些黑土
Kaulder, I know where Belial brought all that dirt.
他租的那臺卡車裝了標準的GPS定位器。
The truck he rented had a standard GPS locator...
妳撒謊！
You lied to me!
妳保存了她的心臟。“回憶起妳的死”。
You saved her heart. "Remember your death."
不是妳想的那樣
It's not what you think.
妳壹直都知道那意味著什麽，妳卻什麽都沒說
You knew what it meant all along, and you said nothing.
因為我不想壹上任就要
Because I wasn't going to be responsible
為十斧會的滅亡負責...
for the dissolution of The Axe and Cross on my very first...
他們正召回女巫王
They're bringing back the Queen.
妳都幹了些什麽！
You don't know what you've done.
我發誓要保守秘密
I swore an oath to keep it secret.
數百年來世界沒有因為這個謊言而毀滅
This lie has kept Apocalypse at bay for hundreds of years.
我們曾擔心如果女巫王的心被毀滅的話
We were afraid if the Queen's heart was destroyed,
妳將會失去妳的永生能力，甚至死掉
you'd lose your immortality. Or die.
那不是妳要做的選擇
That wasn't your choice to make!
那是那個老人的想法
That's what the old man thought.
他被襲擊的那晚
The night he was attacked,
我以為他會毀掉它的
I think he was going to destroy it.
為了妳
For you.
為了解放妳
To set you free.
至少十斧會仍有他們的武器
At least The Axe and Cross still has their weapon.
妳將會侍奉女王
You will serve the Queen...
請不要這樣！
No, please.
由不得妳
Like it or not.
啊！
Ah!
去我的公寓，妳在那很安全。
Go to my apartment. You'll be safe there.
不，說好了我們要在壹起的
No, the deal was that we stick together.
我要自己去，如果我連自己人都不能相信
I'm going alone. If I can't trust
我又怎麽能相信妳呢？
my own people, how the hell can I trust you?
這不像妳
This isn't who you are.
這才是全部的我
It's all I am.
用冷兵器刺她
Pierce her with iron.
用火燒她
Scour her by fire.
就可以讓她真正的死去
Bring her endless death.
我壹直在想妳，考爾德
I've missed you, Kaulder.
這是妳不會明白的
Here's what you don't understand.
妳們種族都不會明白的
What your kind never understood.
我已經仁至義盡了
I've shown mercy.
我本來可以殺光妳們每壹個人的
I could have killed every last one of you.
我已經統計好了
I've done the math.
而且我有的是時間
I've had the time.
妳現在不同了，如此自信
You're different now. So confident.
也許妳不應該讓我永生
Maybe you shouldn't have made me immortal.
考爾德，我來幫忙了。
Kaulder, I came to help.
克洛伊，我告訴過妳不要...
Chloe. I told you not to...
永生的權利從來都不屬於妳，它是我的
Immortality was never yours. It was mine.
妳只是幫我保管而已
You just carried it for me.
直到現在
Until now.
我又重生了
I am reborn.
啊！
Ah!
妳們這個種族...
Your race
總是心存恐懼
has always been frightened.
隱藏在深處
Hiding in caves.
蜷縮在篝火旁
Huddling around fire.
終於
Finally.
嘿，孩子。我還擔心來晚了
Hey, kid. I was afraid I was too late.
我希望自己看起來不像妳這樣難看
I hope I don't look as rough as you do.
好吧
Okay.
我殺了那個詛咒妳的家夥
I killed the one who cursed you.
過來
Here.
喝了這杯
Drink this.
謝謝
Thank you.
女巫王復活了
The Witch Queen has returned.
我曾以為我的永生...
I thought my immortality
是她用來懲罰我的
was the way that she punished me.
但她只是利用我來為她自己保管這種能力
But she just used me to save it for herself.
恐怕我得承擔壹些責任
I'm afraid I bear some responsibility.
這樣想真是過分狂妄了
It was hubris to think
我們的秘密不會被敵人發現
that our secret wouldn't be discovered by the enemy.
我已經預見接下來會發生什麽了
I've seen what comes next.
死亡
Death.
女巫王將會散播更多的詛咒
The Witch Queen will cast another plague curse.
擁有那種力量的女巫們沒有被摧毀嗎？
Haven't covens with that kind of power been destroyed?
我們不再消滅女巫了
We don't destroy witches anymore.
我們監禁她們
We incarcerate them.
我們抓住了所有最有力量的女巫
We took all the most powerful witches
她們曾橫行世上
that ever walked the Earth
把她們關進了壹個地方
and put 'em in one place.
女巫監獄
The witch prison.
她們仍在等待著，等待著被釋放...
And they've been waiting, waiting to be released.
等待著復仇
Waiting to exact revenge.
我們創造了完美的女巫聚會
We created the perfect coven.
現在我回到了原點
Now I'm right back where I started.
妳打敗過她
You defeated her once.
妳還會再次擊敗她
You can defeat her again.
考爾德
Kaulder,
妳得走了
you must go.
妳必須戰鬥
You have to fight.
考爾德
Kaulder.
我從未給它起過名字
I never had a name for it.
但我的敵人都叫它“屠巫劍”
But my enemies came to call it "Hexenbane."
女巫殺手
Witch Slayer.
我也來了
I'm coming, too.
我們約定的前提是能保證妳的安全
Our agreement depended on me keeping you safe.
不，我們約定的是如果我幫助了妳
No, our agreement was that if I helped you,
妳就得保證我的安全
you'd keep me safe.
如果我現在受傷了，我就壹直傷著
If I get hurt now, I stay hurt.
它會好嗎？
Where would that leave you?
妳知道，我不管！
You know, I don't care!
誰說了壹個女巫不能獵殺其他女巫？
Who says that a witch can't hunt witches?
克洛伊...
Chloe.
克勞德...
Kaulder.
這是什麽？
What is this?
這是災難樹。她在這兒。
It's a plague tree. She's here.
當咒語許下
When the spell is done,
鋪天蓋地的蒼蠅將會被釋放
the fly swarm will be released.
我們沒有太多時間了
We haven't much time.
跟緊些
Stay close.
考爾德，犯人去哪了？
Kaulder, where are the prisoners?
天哪！
My God!
每壹個我曾抓到過的女巫
Every witch I ever caught.
女巫正用她們的力量來釋放詛咒
The Queen's using their power to release the plague.
她是怎麽做到的？
How?
用聖歌
The chant.
沒有女巫擁有如此強大的力量，
No witch would be strong enough
能夠單獨施咒。
to cast this spell alone.
但女巫王...
But the Witch Queen's
卻可以將她們的思想像鎖鏈壹樣連起來
linking their minds like a chain.
那我們要怎樣阻止她們呢？
So how do we stop them?
每條鎖鏈都有壹個薄弱的環節
Every chain has a weak link.
- 這個我來吧.-不！
- I'll do the honors. - No.
我們不是要毀掉他的身體
It's not his body we need to destroy.
而是他的意識
It's his mind.
但如果他死在他的夢裏
But if he dies in his dreams,
詛咒將會停止
the plague will be stopped.
我希望還有別的辦法
I wish there was another way.
妳會壹直在這等著我回來，對嗎？
You'll still be here when I get back, right?
妳要單獨去對付女巫王，是嗎？
You're taking on the Queen alone, aren't you?
必須有個了結
It has to end.
嘿！
Hey.
去那兒小心
Be careful in there.
那妳會擔心我嗎？
So are you worried about me then?
唉，我已經習慣妳了
Well, I've gotten used to you.
祝妳獵殺成功
Good hunting.
妳也是
You, too.
守衛
The Sentinel.
它不會停止 除非這個囚犯
And it won't stop until this prisoner
被押他的牢房
is put back in his cell.
它是沖著艾裏克來的
It's coming for Ellic.
考爾德
Kaulder?
如果她有在那邊受到傷害的任何跡象
If there's any sign she's getting hurt in there,
妳必須叫醒她
you have to wake her up.
並且向我保證帶她走得
And promise me you'll get her as far away
越遠越好
from here as you can.
必須的
Of course.
聖歌停下來了
The chanting stopped.
她做到了
She did it.
夢行者向妳展示了過去
A dream-walker shows your past.
只有我能昭示未來
Only I can show the future.
妳們將會失敗，而人類將會墮落
You will fail, and humanity will fall.
我把世界恢復成原來那樣了
I've taken this world back.
還沒有
Not yet.
感覺到了嗎？
Can you feel it?
妳的凡身
Your mortality?
妳的生命正在流逝
Your life ebbing away?
父親
Father!
考爾德
Kaulder.
妳是我們這個世界的入侵者
You are trespassers on our world.
父親
Father!
我已經透過妳的眼睛看到了
I've seen it in your eyes.
妳盼望死亡
You wish for death.
妳明白永生的好處嗎？
You know the benefit of eternal life?
我應該殺死妳兩次的
I get to kill you twice.
快住手！
Stop!
考爾德
Kaulder!
那麽...
Now...
—克洛伊...—對不起
- Chloe... - I'm sorry.
釋放我的女王
Release my Queen.
當我還是個孩子的時候，妳從那些女巫手中將我救出
Those witches you rescued me from when I was a kid...
她們並沒有殺害我的父母，他們就是我的父母
They didn't kill my parents. They were my parents.
但不幸的是，我天生沒有法力。
But sadly, I was born without magic.
妳是個女巫
You're a witch.
是的
Yep.
—不！不！—快回到這兒！
- No! No! - Get back here!
快離開他！放開他！
Get away from him! Let go!
夢行者
Dream-walker.
看看妳自己
Look at you,
妳那醜陋的女巫臉
you ugly bitch of a morning.
妳背叛了那些
You turned against those
妳應該要保護的人們
you were charged with protecting.
是的，女王
Yes, my Queen.
讓我完整吧，幫我到達我的宿命。
Make me whole. Help me reach my destiny.
賜予我魔力吧
Grant me the gift of magic.
沙土不會變成金子
Clay cannot be turned to gold.
沒有法力，妳只是個凡人。
Without magic, you're just a human.
父親？
Father?
親愛的
My love.
妳必須起床了
You must get up.
父親，妳得起床了
Father, you need to get up.
去救他們
Save them.
去吧！親愛的，去戰鬥吧！
Go, my love. Fight.
妳還在垂死掙紮
You cling to your pathetic life.
為了什麽呢？
And for what reason?
最親近的人背叛了妳
Those closest to you betray you,
而那些妳宣誓要保護的對象甚至都不知道妳的名字
and those you claim to protect don't even know your name.
用鋼鐵
By iron
和烈火
and fire!
試著用ipad來做吧
Try doing that with an iPad.
考爾德
Kaulder!
Kaulder?
考爾德
只要心臟還在跳動
As long as the Hexen heart beats,
她就不會真的死去
she's never truly dead.
不，妳不要！妳會死的
No, you can't! You'll die.
我已經準備好面對現實了
I'm ready to face that reality.
不！壹定有別的辦法
No! There must be another way.
聽我說
Listen to me.
當我被拉入黑暗中時
When I was pulled into the shadows,
我看見了比她更可怕的東西
I saw that there were things much worse than her.
在黑暗中，靜靜等候
In the darkness. Waiting.
等待什麽？
Waiting for what?
壹個沒有妳的世界
The world without you.
我們仍需要妳
We still need you.
我需要妳
I need you.
十斧會背叛了我
The Axe and Cross betrayed me.
我不再相信任何人
I can't trust anyone.
妳可以相信我
You can trust me.
我已經在這條路上走了800年
800 years I've been on this road.
壹直在狩獵
Always hunting.
壹直是...孑然壹人
- Always... - Alone.
不會再是了
You wouldn't be.
另外
Besides,
妳還欠我5萬塊
you still owe me fifty thousand dollars.
5千塊
Five thousand.
好吧，這麽說我們是在砍價了，是嗎？
Oh. So we're negotiating, then?
十斧會將很頭疼
The Axe and Cross would be bothered that
她們不再擁有
they're no longer in possession
女巫王的心臟
of the Queen's heart.
我不再幫十斧會工作了
I don't serve The Axe and Cross anymore.
這次我為自己而做的
This time I do it for me.
好吧，這是關於時間
Well, it's about time.
我過去總認為
You know, I used to think
宇宙循環往復、周而復始
the universe ran in endless circles,
總在重復著自身，永遠可以預測
always repeating itself, always predictable.
那現在呢
And now?
我不知道接下來會發生什麽
I don't know what happens next.
妳知道我們凡人怎麽稱它嗎
Do you know what we mortals call that?
生活
Living.
妳知道
You know,
我仍需要妳
I still need you.
那麽
Well, then
我為妳效勞
I'm at your service.
得了吧，妳不會再年輕了
Come on. You're not getting any younger.
妳是準備走，還是怎樣
So you ready to go, or what?
我來開車
I'm driving.
好吧
Okay.
謝謝觀賞
本電影由 BT首發論壇 原創壓制
www.BTshoufa.com